<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE xliff PUBLIC "-//XLIFF//DTD XLIFF//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/committees/xliff/documents/xliff.dtd">
<xliff version="1.0">
  <file source-language="en" target-language="ru" datatype="plaintext" original="ew-messages" product-name="ew-messages">
    <header/>
    <body>
      <trans-unit id="1">
        <source>bongbong.subject</source>
        <target>Bongbong</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="2">
        <source>eu20130513forum.subject</source>
        <target>Forum Reminder</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="3">
        <source>7dayspeedupsale.subject</source>
        <target/>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="4">
        <source>bongbong.from</source>
        <target>Mister X</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="5">
        <source>bongbong.body</source>
        <target>&#x41F;&#x440;&#x438;&#x43C;&#x435;&#x440; &#x441;&#x43E;&#x43E;&#x431;&#x449;&#x435;&#x43D;&#x438;&#x44F;: Zivio!</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="6">
        <source>mass-assignment.subject</source>
        <target>Maps Mostly Restored</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="7">
        <source>7dayspeedupsale.body</source>
        <target/>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="8">
        <source>body.blackmarketinshop</source>
        <target>For a VERY limited time, the Black Market Patch will be available to purchase in the Shop!  Visit the featured tab for your chance to pick one up!

The Black Market Patch will GUARANTEE upgrades to your Engineering Lab Parts up to Level 16 and 17!

This item will be featured at the low price of 225 Platinum and there is NO limit to the number you can buy!  Stock up today!</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="9">
        <source>body.marketcrash</source>
        <target>For a VERY limited time, the Market Crash Mystery Box will be available to purchase in the Shop! Visit the featured tab for your chance to pick one up!

The Market Crash will GUARANTEE 1 Black Market Patch which upgrades your Engineering Lab Parts up to Level 16, 17 and 18!

Also a chance to win 2, 3, 5 or 10 Black Market Patches!

This item will be featured at the low price of 149 Platinum, stock up today!</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="10">
        <source>mass-assignment.from</source>
        <target>Mister X</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="11">
        <source>mass-assignment.body</source>
        <target>Maps are now available again on all sectors except Orion and Cygnus, which we expect to restore within 12-24 hours. 

Sorry for the interruption of service. We'll have a more comprehensive report by noon tomorrow Pacific time. 

Thank you for your patience.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="12">
        <source>outage20120209.subject</source>
        <target>&#x417;&#x430;&#x43F;&#x43B;&#x430;&#x43D;&#x438;&#x440;&#x43E;&#x432;&#x430;&#x43D;&#x43D;&#x43E;&#x435; &#x442;&#x435;&#x445;&#x43D;&#x438;&#x447;&#x435;&#x441;&#x43A;&#x43E;&#x435; &#x43E;&#x431;&#x441;&#x43B;&#x443;&#x436;&#x438;&#x432;&#x430;&#x43D;&#x438;&#x435; &#x432;&#x441;&#x435;&#x445; &#x441;&#x435;&#x43A;&#x442;&#x43E;&#x440;&#x43E;&#x432;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="13">
        <source>body.mysterybox17</source>
        <target>Looking to add a Concussive Effect to your turrets?  The new Frozen Token will stop attacking troops in their tracks!  Enhance your Turrets with the Frozen Token to add the Concussive Effect to any of your turrets!

Open this Mystery Box for a chance to win the Frozen Token!  Prizes also include Level 5 Frozen E-Lab Parts, Black Market Patches, Hacker&#x2019;s Patches, Incendiary Cores, Generals SP 1000 and Troop Bundles!

This box will only be available for a limited time so be sure to pick one up and start freezing your enemy attacks today!
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="14">
        <source>eu20130513forum.body</source>
        <target>Greetings Commanders,

The Edgeworld Community Team would like to remind all our fellow players that we have been working on the forum features: new content have been posted recently and there&#x2019;s a lot more to come.

Our intention is to treat the player community with the deserved care and attention, in order to get your involvement not only as gamers, but also as community participants. We will be giving answers to your troubles when needed, adding more useful information and posting new funny events to make the whole experience of playing Edgeworld something even more awesome!

We sincerely hope to see you participating in these events and contests, there will be rewards and achievements for those who will join the forum activities. Commanders, this is the beginning of a new era in Edgeworld&#x2019;s Forum!



These are the links of the dedicated forums for each language:

ENGLISH

For more information click &lt;a href=" http://community.kabam.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?127-Edgeworld " target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;

GERMAN

F&#xFC;r mehr informationen klicken sie &lt;a href=" http://community.kabam.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?389-Deutsch " target="_blank"&gt;hier&lt;/a&gt;

SPANISH

Para m&#xE1;s informaci&#xF3;n click &lt;a href=" http://community.kabam.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?425-Espa%C3%B1ol " target="_blank"&gt;aqu&#xED;&lt;/a&gt;

ITALIAN

Per saperne di pi&#xF9; clicca &lt;a href=" http://community.kabam.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?413-Italiano " target="_blank"&gt;qui&lt;/a&gt;

FRENCH

Pour plus d'informations clique &lt;a href=" http://community.kabam.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?401-Francais " target="_blank"&gt; ici&lt;/a&gt;



Regards,


Edgeworld Community Team</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="15">
        <source>outage20120209.body</source>
        <target>&#x41A;&#x43E;&#x43C;&#x430;&#x43D;&#x434;&#x438;&#x440;!

&#x421;&#x435;&#x433;&#x43E;&#x434;&#x43D;&#x44F; &#x432; 20:00 PST &#x432;&#x43E; &#x432;&#x441;&#x435;&#x445; &#x441;&#x435;&#x43A;&#x442;&#x43E;&#x440;&#x430;&#x445; Edgeworld &#x431;&#x443;&#x434;&#x435;&#x442; &#x43F;&#x440;&#x43E;&#x432;&#x43E;&#x434;&#x438;&#x442;&#x44C;&#x441;&#x44F; &#x442;&#x435;&#x445;&#x43D;&#x438;&#x447;&#x435;&#x441;&#x43A;&#x43E;&#x435; &#x43E;&#x431;&#x441;&#x43B;&#x443;&#x436;&#x438;&#x432;&#x430;&#x43D;&#x438;&#x435;. &#x421;&#x432;&#x44F;&#x437;&#x44C; &#x431;&#x443;&#x434;&#x435;&#x442; &#x432;&#x43E;&#x441;&#x441;&#x442;&#x430;&#x43D;&#x43E;&#x432;&#x43B;&#x435;&#x43D;&#x430; &#x432; 20:30 PST.

Edgeworld</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="16">
        <source>body.20140121forcetourney</source>
        <target>A NEW Force Tournament has begun!

A Brand New 3-Day Force Tournament has begun! This Tournament features a 3x Boost to all Force Points earned through Training, and 10x Boost to all Force Points earned through Building!

The Top 4 Finishers will get Prizes, Platinum and Trophies! Additional prizes all the way to 40th place! Check out the Leaderboard to see the updated prizes and stay tuned for a special announcement tomorrow!

Good Luck!

--The Edgeworld Team</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="17">
        <source>subject.mysterybox17</source>
        <target>Get the New Frozen Token!</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="18">
        <source>subject.level18release</source>
        <target>The HIGHLY ANTICIPATED Level 18 is here!!!</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="19">
        <source>body.20140219BMP</source>
        <target>The Black Market Patch is available to purchase in the Shop. Visit the featured tab for your chance to pick one up! It&#x2019;s only up for a LIMITED TIME so act fast!

The Black Market Patch will GUARANTEE upgrades to your Engineering Lab Parts up to Level 16 and 17!

This item will be featured at the low price of 199 Platinum and there is NO limit to the number you can buy! Stock up today!</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="20">
        <source>body.level18release</source>
        <target>The long awaited Level 18 is here, and with a ton of new additions! You will see a greater increase in the power of your Troops, Buildings, Engineering Lab Parts and Generals,, and significantly increased Warp Gate capacities at Level 18, so it is essential that you start upgrading your base today!

In order to access these new levels, you need The Ruby Core.

The war for Cerulea IV is going to a whole new level of excitement, capitalize on all of the technology advancements and upgrade today!!</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="21">
        <source>body.20140219bmp</source>
        <target>The Black Market Patch is available to purchase in the Shop. Visit the featured tab for your chance to pick one up! It&#x2019;s only up for a LIMITED TIME so act fast!

The Black Market Patch will GUARANTEE upgrades to your Engineering Lab Parts up to Level 16 and 17!

This item will be featured at the low price of 249 Platinum and there is NO limit to the number you can buy! Stock up today!</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="22">
        <source>subject.20140121forcetourney</source>
        <target>10x Building and 3x Training Tourney!</target>
      </trans-unit>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>
