<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE xliff PUBLIC "-//XLIFF//DTD XLIFF//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/committees/xliff/documents/xliff.dtd">
<xliff version="1.0">
  <file source-language="en" target-language="ru" datatype="plaintext" original="ew-outage" product-name="ew-outage">
    <header/>
    <body>
      <trans-unit id="1">
        <source>08312011b.body</source>
        <target>The Edgeworld team continues to investigate issues caused by our maintenance Wednesday. Due to the widespread nature of these issues, all players on all sectors will be compensated fully for their potential time and resource losses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each player will receive, in each sector they play in:&lt;br&gt;Two 2.5-Day Accelerators&lt;br&gt;4 Million each of Crystal, Gas, Energy, and Uranium, as items&lt;br&gt;These items should already be in your inventory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These items should allow you to regain any lost resources and advance any lost research or upgrades back to where they should be.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have any continuing problems, please use the Help buttons to send a message to our support team, and we'll respond to you as quickly as possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a side effect of this incident, some players at random may have experienced doubled building upgrades or unit training. We will &lt;u&gt;not&lt;/u&gt; be attempting to reclaim these accidental benefits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you once again for your patience.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="2">
        <source>09012011.subject</source>
        <target>Additional Resources for Advanced Players</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="3">
        <source>08312011b.subject</source>
        <target>August 31 Outage Update</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="4">
        <source>09012011.body</source>
        <target>After sending out our compensation package Wednesday to all players, we decided that high-level players should receive additional compensation for their losses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We will be granting an additional four 4 Million Resource items each of Crystal, Gas, Energy, and Uranium to each player with a level 7 or 8 Command Center, a total of 64 million resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This should allow you to refill your Storage Depots and restart any upgrades, training, and research which were interrupted by this event. Thank you for your understanding and patience during this time.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="5">
        <source>08312011.body</source>
        <target>Due to an unplanned maintenance event, Edgeworld was unaccessible for a brief period on Wednesday. We apologize for the interruption in service.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This maintenance may have affected construction and upgrades that started or finished during the maintenance period. We believe that we have resolved a majority of the issues from this incident. If you have any continuing issues, please send our support team a message using the Help buttons above and below the game window.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you for your patience while we continue to upgrade and improve Edgeworld! &lt;a href="http://community.kabam.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?127" target="_blank"&gt;Please visit our forums&lt;/a&gt; for more information as it becomes available.
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="6">
        <source>08312001.subject</source>
        <target>Unplanned Maintenance</target>
      </trans-unit>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>
